http://www.goinglobal.com/privacy-policy

Register for a Demo
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Non-disclosure of personal information, including names of personal account holders, to the subscribing organization is protected by this policy.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Updated July 2017
Search Jobs
Select CountryArgentinaAustraliaAustriaBahrainBelgiumBrazilCanadaChileChinaColombiaCosta RicaCzech RepublicDenmarkEcuadorEgyptFinlandFranceGermanyGreeceHong KongHungaryIndiaIndonesiaIrelandIsraelItalyJapanKuwaitLuxembourgMalaysiaMexicoMoroccoNetherlandsNew ZealandNigeriaNorwayOmanPakistanPanamaPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalQatarRomaniaRussiaSaudi ArabiaSingaporeSouth AfricaSouth KoreaSpainSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwanThailandTurkeyUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayVenezuelaVietnam
GoinGlobal Provides Career and Employment Resources for:
Join us for an online demo and receive complimentary access to GoinGlobalRegister Now
